easytolet.in 2018-02-18

# Privacy Policy - Easytolet.in

###### This Privacy Policy applies to the www.Easytolet.in

www.Easytolet.in recognises the importance of maintaining your privacy. We value your privacy and appreciate your trust in us. This Policy describes how we treat user information we collect on www.Easytolet.in and other offline sources. This Privacy Policy applies to current and former visitors to our website and to our online customers. By visiting and/or using our website, you agree to this Privacy Policy. 

www.Easytolet.in is a property of RR Techpath India Pvt. Ltd., a Partnership Firm having its office at, CVR Chambers, 6th Floor, Labbipet, Vijayawada, Andhra Pradesh - 520008. 

###### Information We Collect 

Contact information. We might collect your Name,Email,Phone,Address,IP Address. 

Demographic information. We may collect demographic information about you or any other information provided by your during the use of our website. We might collect this as a part of a survey also. 

###### We Collect Information In Different Ways.

We collect information directly from you. We collect information directly from you when you contact us. We also collect information if you post a comment on our websites or ask us a question through phone or email.

###### Use Of Your Personal Information 

We use information to respond to your requests or questions. We might use your information to confirm your registration for an event or contest. 

We use information to improve our products and services. We might use your information to customize your experience with us. This could include displaying content based upon your preferences. 

We use information to look at site trends and customer interests. We may use your information to make our website and products better. We may combine information we get from you with information about you we get from third parties.

We use information for security purposes. We may use information to protect our company, our customers, or our websites. 

We use information as otherwise permitted by law.

###### Sharing Of Information With Third-Parties 

###### Email Opt-Out

You can opt out of receiving our marketing emails. To stop receiving our promotional emails, please email unsubscribe@easytolet.in It may take about ten days to process your request. Even if you opt out of getting marketing messages, we will still be sending you transactional messages through email and SMS about your purchases. 

###### Grievance Officer 

In accordance with Information Technology Act 2000 and rules made there under, the name and contact details of the Grievance Officer are provided below: 

Easytolet.in   
CVR Chambers  
6th Floor, Labbipet  
Vijayawada  
Andhra Pradesh - 520008.   
Phone: +91 - 45 46 47 48   
Email: [support@Easytolet.in](mailto:support@Easytolet.in)

If you have any questions about this Policy or other privacy concerns, you can also email us at [support@Easytolet.in](mailto:support@Easytolet.in)

###### Updates To This Policy 

This Privacy Policy was last updated on 1st March, 2016. From time to time we may change our privacy practices. We will notify you of any material changes to this policy as required by law. We will also post an updated copy on our website. Please check our site periodically for updates. 

###### Jurisdiction 

If you choose to visit the website, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Policy and the website's terms of use. In addition to the foregoing, any disputes arising under this Policy shall be governed by the laws of India.
